A man's tradition every woman should know about.
Bachelor Party is a comedy film directed by Neal Israel.
On the eve of his wedding to his longtime girlfriend, unassuming nice guy
Rick is dragged out for a night of debauchery by his friends.
Rick Gassko, played by Tom Hanks.
Debbie Thompson, played by Tawny Kitaen.
Jay O'Neill, played by Adrian Zmed.
Ed Thompson, played by George Grizzard.
Mrs. Thompson, played by Barbara Stuart.
Cole Whittier, played by Robert Prescott.
Bachelor Party is a 1984 American sex comedy film directed by Neal Israel, written by Israel and
Pat Proft, and starring Tom Hanks, Adrian Zmed, William Tepper, and Tawny Kitaen.
The film revolves around a bachelor party that a group of men throw for their friend Rick Gassko (Hanks) on
the eve of his wedding and whether he can remain faithful to his fiancée Debbie (Kitaen).
The film explores themes of bachelor, loyalty, donkey, stag night, wedding.
The tone is lighthearted.